fas.org 2016-10-19

# Privacy Policy - Federation Of American Scientists

The Federation of American Scientists (FAS) respects your right to privacy and is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. FAS does not sell or rent any information you provide us through our website. We do not collect any information from you without your knowledge and permission, and we do not ask that you enter any personal information to access or use most areas of the FAS website. In order to use some of the tools and functions, such as to subscribe to the electronic newsletters or to comment on FAS weblogs, you must enter some identifying information. Information you provide FAS is stored in a secure location and is accessible only by designated staff.

We have created the following privacy policy to inform you about the ways in which we collect and use this information.

### FAS Mailing Lists:

FAS provides timely updates to our website users via email. We collect relevant contact information and enable you to self-select the type of information you’d like to receive. You will be able to unsubscribe from communications you receive from us by following the directions included with each email alert.

### Weblog Comments:

If you disclose personally identifiable information on publicly-accessible areas of an FAS site (such as the Secrecy News Blog or Strategic Security Blog), this information may become public. FAS does not control the acts of other visitors to its sites, so please be cautious when deciding to reveal personal information on a public area of any site.

### Forwarding Pages via Email:

To forward an article or page you must enter your name, your email address and the email address(es) of the recipient (s). FAS includes your name and email address when we send your message.

### Secure Transactions:

FAS appreciates and will accept online contributions. When you join or donate to FAS via our website your donation information is encrypted and transmitted via a secure connection. FAS uses your credit card information only for the purpose of processing your donation. We will not disclose this information except as necessary to process your donation and we do not store it once your donation has been processed.

### Donation Delivery and Refund Policy:

All online donors to the Federation of American Scientists will receive an email receipt confirming the donation for tax deductible purposes. FAS Members (donors of at least $50, or $25 for students) will receive a donation receipt and membership information at the Mailing Address provided.

The Federation of American Scientists is a non-profit organization that exists to provide non-partisan technical analysis on international security, science, and technology issues to policy makers, the press, and the public. Refunds of your gift are discouraged. However, if there is a clear error in the amount of payment or payee, please contact FAS within 30 days from the date of donation at 202-454-4694 to resolve.

### Security

FAS uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving sensitive personal and financial data from our site. Please note, however, that security breaches can occur even if reasonable steps are taken to prevent such breaches; for example, we cannot guarantee that information provided through our sites will not be illegally accessed on our servers or intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Please contact us if you believe there has been any breach of the security of our website.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please fell free to call 202-546-3300 or email us at: fas@fas.org.

You can also reach us via U.S. Mail at:

Federation of American Scientists  
1725 DeSales Street, NW  
6th Floor  
Washington, DC 20036
